{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590664022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590664022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590667609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590667609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590671016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590671016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590674402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590674402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590677714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590677714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590680670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590680670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590684217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590684216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590687702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590687702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590690631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590690631"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590693486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590693486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590696688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590696687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590701236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590701236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590704254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590704254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590707919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590707919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590711200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590711200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590714405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590714405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590717721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590717721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590720900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590720900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590723916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590723915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590726839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590726839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590729947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590729946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590733452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590733452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590738678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590738677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590746321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590746321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590752072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590752071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590758340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590758339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590768429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590768429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 44ba4690-0b8d-4434-ae98-23b61cf799b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590777376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590777376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 694ef519-64c9-458c-a476-e3e395a11efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590783107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590783106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 694ef519-64c9-458c-a476-e3e395a11efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590790315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590790314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 694ef519-64c9-458c-a476-e3e395a11efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590796673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590796673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 694ef519-64c9-458c-a476-e3e395a11efc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-5-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590806814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590806814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" f7f85997-afec-47c5-916b-27223636cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590808955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590808954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" f7f85997-afec-47c5-916b-27223636cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590810101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590810101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" f7f85997-afec-47c5-916b-27223636cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590810156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590810156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" f7f85997-afec-47c5-916b-27223636cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590828654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590828654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" f7f85997-afec-47c5-916b-27223636cf17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590840160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590840160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590844032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590844032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590845591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590845591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590849564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590849564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" familia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590851133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590851132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590854153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590854153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fupi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590855714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590855714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590859384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590859384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590860925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590860925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590864186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590864186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590865736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590865736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590868981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590868981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590870991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590870991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548590871154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548590871154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_150409"," gameId":" 83406da6-55a9-4c71-a508-83f34a227b6b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.45"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fulana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}